Guide to the E. L. Wolven Glass Plate Negative Collection, 1897-1944
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series VII. Founder's Day, 1900-1935
  - Founder's Day, 1924
    - Founder's Day — Students in stereotypical Asian costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1924 May 2 (Box 32 [Box263_021])
  - Founder's Day, 1925
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925 at the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108c])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925 at the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108d])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925 marching to the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925 marching toward the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108b])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925 performing at the song contest on the steps of Student's Building, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109d])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1925's conductor at the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108f])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1926 performing at the song contest on the steps of Student's Building, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109e])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 at the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109c])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 performing in the song contest on the steps of Student's Building, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108e])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108j])
    - Founder's Day — Student baseball team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 11 [Package083_004])
    - Founder's Day — Student dressed as a pirate at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 11 [Package083_002])
    - Founder's Day — Student dressed as a pirate at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 11 [Package083_003])
    - Founder's Day — Student dressed in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 11 [Package083_001])
    - Founder's Day — Student in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 14 [Package092_011])
    - Founder's Day — Student in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108])
    - Founder's Day — Student wearing dark makeup and dressed as a pirate at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109g])
    - Founder's Day — Students at the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109j])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as a pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 14 [Package092_012])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as crew boat racers with field hockey sticks as paddles, 1925 May 1 (Box 21 [package110h])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 14 [Package092_005])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108g])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108h])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109f])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109h])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as pirates at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109i])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed in costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 14 [Package092_001])
    - Founder's Day — Students handing out copies of the Vassar Vagabond, some dressed as pirates, 1925 May 1 (Box 22 [package115g])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package108i])
    - Founder's Day — Students performing in the song contest, 1925 May 1 (Box 20 [package109b])
  - Founder's Day, 1926
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1929 at the song contest, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 37/38 [Box271_018])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 41 [Box276_014])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken giving the Founder's Day address on the steps of Students Building, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 35 [Box267_002])
    - Founder's Day — Song contest, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 34 [Box266_013])
    - Founder's Day — Student team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 33/34 [Box265_001])
    - Founder's Day — Students in 1890s costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 35 [Box267_003])
    - Founder's Day — Students in 1890s costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 35 [Box267_004])
    - Founder's Day — Students in 1890s costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 35 [Box267_005])
    - Founder's Day — Students in 1890s costumes at the faculty-student baseball game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 21 [package110k])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume playing a bocci-like game, 1926 Apr 30 (Box 21 [package110f])
  - Founder's Day, 1927
    - Founder’s Day — Class of 1928 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_004])
    - Founder’s Day — Students in costume including four in stereotypical Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 37/38 [Box271_006])
    - Founder’s Day — Students in costume, one in stereotypical Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_007])
    - Founder’s Day — Students in costume, one on a horse. Others are in what might have been intended to represent Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 37/38 [Box271_015])
    - Founder’s Day — Two students in costume on a horse. One of the students is in what might have been intended to represent Romani dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 37/38 [Box271_005])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_010])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 13 [Package088_006])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package104])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package104b])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1927 marching to the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_008])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1928 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 13 [Package088_003])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1928 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_008])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1929 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105i])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1930 at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105h])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_007])
    - Founder's Day — Song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_009])
    - Founder's Day — Song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 12 [Package087_011])
    - Founder's Day — Song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 21 [package111])
    - Founder's Day — Student in costume on a horse and another in what might have been intended to represent Romani dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_009])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_002])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_003])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_005])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package104c])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105e])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, one in stereotypical Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105g])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, three in stereotypical Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_006])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, two in stereotypical Native American dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package104d])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, two in stereotypical Native American dress, another in what might have been intended to represent Romani dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 15 [Package094_001])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, two in stereotypical Native American dress, one in dark makeup, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 13 [Package088_005])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, two in what might have been intended to represent Romani dress, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105d])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume, one in stereotypical Native American dress, three are wearing stereotypical Romani costumes, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 19 [package105j])
    - Founder's Day — Woman with a child at the song contest, 1927 Apr 29 (Box 13 [Package088_001])
  - Founder's Day, 1928
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1928 at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_001])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1928 marching toward the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_002])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1928 performing at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 23 [package116c])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1929 at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 35 [Box267_012])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1929 at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_004])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1929 performing at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 35 [Box267_011])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1930 performing at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_005])
    - Founder's Day — Class of 1930 performing at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 24 [package119])
    - Founder's Day — Dean C. Mildred and her dog at the faculty-student baseball game. A student dressed in stereotypical Indian costume is also pictured, and may be in dark makeup, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_011])
    - Founder's Day — Members of the Class of 1930 with the banner for best song at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_008])
    - Founder's Day — Student conductor at the song contest, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_007])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package099_003])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package099_005])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package099_006])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package099_012])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_003])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_006])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_010])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 23 [package116b])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game. One is dressed in stereotypical Indian costume and may be in brownface. The other's costume may be meant to represent that of a Romani woman, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_012])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume at the faculty-student baseball game. One is wearing a stereotypical Romani costume, 1928 Apr 27 (Box 17 [Package100_009])
  - Founder's Day, 1929
    - Founder's Day — A student riding in the bicycle contest, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_003])
    - Founder's Day — A student riding in the bicycle contest, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_007])
    - Founder's Day — A student riding in the bicycle contest, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_009])
    - Founder's Day — A student riding in the bicycle contest, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_010])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_007])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 11 [Package084_001])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 11 [Package084_002])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 11 [Package084_008])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_005])
    - Founder's Day — Henry Noble MacCracken at bat at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 41 [Box276_020])
    - Founder's Day — Henry Noble MacCracken at bat at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_003])
    - Founder's Day — Henry Noble MacCracken at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 37/38 [Box271_019])
    - Founder's Day — Professor at bat in the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_006])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators and judges at the Founder's Day contests. One of the judges may be Professor Frances Gertrude Wick or Dean C. Mildred Thompson, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package034_004])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_001])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_002])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_001])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_002])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the Founder's Day contests, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_004])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the Founder's Day contests, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_009])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the Founder's Day contests, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_008])
    - Founder's Day — Spectators at the Founder's Day contests. One seated faculty member is in stereotypical Asian costume, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 11 [Package084_006])
    - Founder's Day — Students in a horse-drawn carriage for the Founder's Day parade, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_008])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume with signs about the "Milly A. Wimpfheimer Farm," "Rowdy the Ricket" and Sally the "Scarletina Sister.,", 1929 Apr 26 (Box 11 [Package084_009])
    - Founder's Day — Students lined up for a bicycle contest, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_010])
    - Founder's Day — The faculty team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 24/25 [package 121i])
    - Founder's Day — The students' team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 24/25 [package 121j])
    - Founder's Day — The students' team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 14 [Package091_006])
    - Founder's Day — Two students in costume, one in a baby carriage, 1929 Apr 26 (Box 8 [Package033_005])
  - Founder's Day, 1930
    - Founder's Day — An unidentified woman placing a wreath on Georgia A Kendrick's grave at the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, which was visited by a contingent from Vassar on Founder's Day, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 24/25 [package 121h])
    - Founder's Day — An unidentified woman placing a wreath on President James Monroe Taylor's grave at the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, which was visited by a contingent from Vassar on Founder's Day, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 21 [package110i])
    - Founder's Day — Dean C. Mildred Thompson at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 24 [package119b])
    - Founder's Day — Dean C. Mildred Thompson at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 26 [package149f])
    - Founder's Day — Dean C. Mildred Thompson dressed in wings and a halo at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_008])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty team at the faculty-student baseball game, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_011])
    - Founder's Day — Matthew Vassar's grave, Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, which was visited by a contingent from Vassar on Founder's Day, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 24 [package119c])
    - Founder's Day — President James Monroe Taylor's grave at the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, visited by a contingent from Vassar on Founder's Day, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_008])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken at Georgia A. Kendrick's grave in the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package082_003])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken at Matthew Vassar's grave in the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package082_002])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken at the faculty-student baseball game, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package082_001])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken dressed in a stereotypical Middle Eastern costume and a student at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_006])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken dressed in a stereotypical Middle Eastern costume and Dean C. Mildred Thompson at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_006])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken dressed in a stereotypical Middle Eastern costume and Dean C. Mildred Thompson at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 21 [package110j])
    - Founder's Day — President MacCracken speaking at Matthew Vassar's grave at the Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, listened to by a contingent of visitors from Vassar, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_004])
    - Founder's Day — Student at bat in the faculty-student baseball game, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_005])
    - Founder's Day — Student players from the faculty-student baseball game, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_003])
    - Founder's Day — Students dressed as skeletons for the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_002])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_009])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_010])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 26 [package149i])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, one dressed as Charlie Chaplin, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_007])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day Parade, one in stereotypical Native American dress, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 21 [package110l])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, two dressed as ghosts, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_001])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade, two dressed as ghosts, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_007])
    - Founder's Day — Students in costume for the Founder's Day parade. Four are dressed as an elephant, and a fifth is in stereotypical Indian costume, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 11 [Package083_012])
    - Founder's Day — Unidentified woman at the festivities after the Founder's Day parade, 1930 Apr 25 (Box 12 [Package085_005])
  - Founder's Day, circa 1932-1935
    - Founder's Day — Professor Lucy Maynard Salmon's grave, Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, approximately 1932 (Box 11 [Package083_010])
    - Founder's Day — Professor Lucy Maynard Salmon's grave, Poughkeepsie Rural Cemetery, approximately 1932 (Box 12 [Package085_009])
    - Founder's Day — Faculty-student baseball game, played behind Josselyn Hall, 1935 (Box 35 [Box267_009])
- Series VIII. Miscellaneous Vassar, 1900-1940
  - John Burroughs and Vassar College students at Slabsides — Copy photograph of John Burroughs and students at Slabsides. The students could be members of the Wake Robin Club, 1900-1911 (Box 44 [Box280_018])
  - Student group behind Main Building — Copy photograph of a group of unidentified students standing behind Main Building, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package019_008])
  - Student group on a dock — Copy photograph of a student group on a dock. Could be a trip to West Point, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package019_006])
  - Student group on steps — Copy photograph of an unidentified group of students sitting on steps, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_013])
  - Student group outside in hats — Copy photograph of an unidentified group of students sitting outside wearing heavy coats and hats, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_014])
  - Student on a bicycle — Unidentified student riding a bicycle, 1900-1910 (Box 43/44 [Box279_025])
  - Students outside wearing fur wraps — Copy photograph of two students outside one of the dorms in winter coats and furs, 1900-1910 (Box 28 [package156h])
  - Students sitting on dorm steps — Students sitting on the steps of either Davison or Raymond, 1900-1910 (Box 28 [package156i])
  - Vassar College student group outside in turtlenecks — Copy photograph of an unidentified group of students outside in turtlenecks, possibly at Lake Mohonk, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_012])
  - Vassar student leaning on a branch — Copy photograph of an unidentified student in a wooded area leaning on a branch, possibly at Lake Mohonk, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package019_002])
  - Vassar students outside in turtlenecks — Copy photograph a group of students outside in turtlenecks, possibly at Lake Mohonk, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package019_007])
  - Vassar students outside in turtlenecks having a picnic — Copy photograph a group of students outside in turtlenecks having a picnic, possibly at Lake Mohonk, 1900-1910 (Box 28 [package156g])
  - Woman and steam car — Copy photograph of a woman putting water in a steam-powered automobile, 1900-1910 (Box 5 [Package018_003])
  - Young men and women on a boat — Copy photograph of three men and three women. The women are likely Vassar College students, 1900-1910 (Box 28 [package156k])
  - Mary D. Dodge — Copy photograph of an 1877 photograph of Mary D. Dodge (VC 1901), aged 16 months, 1900-1940 (Box 99 [Box260_003])
  - Two women on horses, one in costume — Two unidentified women on horses, one in costume, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_014])
  - Woman in costume on a horse — Unidentified woman in costume on a horse, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_012])
  - Woman in costume on a horse — Unidentified woman in costume on a horse, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_015])
  - Woman on a horse — Unidentified woman on a horse, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_011])
  - Woman on a horse — Unidentified woman on a horse, 1910-1940 (Box 42/43 [Box278_013])
  - Singing on the steps of Students' Building — Unidentified group, possibly a mix of students and alumnae, on the steps of Students' Building, 1915-1920 (Box 33 [Box264_015])
  - Shorthand class — Teacher at the chalkboard and students with what look like stenography pads. May be one of the preparedness courses Vassar offered after the United States entered World War I, approximately 1917 (Box 98 [Box259_005])
  - Helen Rose (VC 1918) — Helen St. John Perrott Rose, Class of 1918, President of the Vassar Christian Association, standing at a bulletin board, 1917-1918 (Box 98 [Box259_014])
  - Liberty Loan Campaign — Photos of students taken to advertise Liberty loans. Featured were a baseball game against the Kaiser, and portrayals of Mary Pickford, Douglas Fairbanks and Charlie Chaplin, 1918 (Box 78/79 [231_11])
  - Liberty Loan Campaign — Photos of students taken to advertise Liberty loans. Featured were a baseball game against the Kaiser, and portrayals of Mary Pickford, Douglas Fairbanks and Charlie Chaplin, 1918 (Box 78/79 [231_12])
  - Liberty Loan Campaign — Photos of students taken to advertise Liberty loans. Featured were a baseball game against the Kaiser, and portrayals of Mary Pickford, Douglas Fairbanks and Charlie Chaplin, 1918 (Box 78/79 [231_18])
  - Liberty Loan Campaign — Photos of students taken to advertise Liberty loans. Featured were a baseball game against the Kaiser, and portrayals of Mary Pickford, Douglas Fairbanks and Charlie Chaplin, 1918 (Box 78/79 [231_19])
  - Liberty Loan Campaign — Photos of students taken to advertise Liberty loans. Featured were a baseball game against the Kaiser, and portrayals of Mary Pickford, Douglas Fairbanks and Charlie Chaplin, 1918 (Box 39/40 [Box274_001])